guardster.com 2007-12-10

# Guardster - Privacy Policy

Effective 12/01/04

**Guardster** Privacy Notice Table of Contents: 

  * Our Commitment to Privacy
  * The Information We Collect
  * How We Use Information
  * Our Commitment to Data Security
  * Our Commitment to Children's Privacy
  * How to Contact Us

**Our Commitment to Privacy**  
Your privacy is as important to us as your business. In order to insure your privacy we are providing this notice to explain our information collection practices. 

**The Information We Collect**  
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Guardster website. On some pages you can request information or use our services. The types of personal information that may be collected at these pages are: 

  * Email address 
  * Username for your account 
  * Password for your account 

**How We Use Information**  
The Guardster Subscription service does not collect, track nor retain any information about who uses it, their IP addresses or the uses to which it is put. User authentication is used only to allow access to the subscription service. 

On the Guardster website, we use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and services and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website. We do not disclose anything that could be used to identify individual users. 

On the Guardster FREE webproxy, we use keywords from websites visited using the FREE webproxy, as well as the user's IP address to target ads, but once the user session is ended, the server automatically erases all information temporarily stored, such as user IP addresses and websites visited. We do not disclose anything that could be used to identify individual users. 

Any personally identifying information is retained on our servers only long enough to support the function being provided and then the server promptly erases it once the user session is over. It is not shared with other organizations for commercial or any other purposes. 

Newsletter signups are used for the purpose of sending an emailed newsletter. 

With respect to cookies: We use cookies only to assist in serving advertising on the website and the Guardster FREE webproxy service, NOT on the Guardster Subscription service.. 

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages and the Guardster FREE webproxy service. As a result of your visit to our site or use of the Guardster FREE webproxy service, ad server companies may place cookies on your computer. We are not responsible for cookies they put on your machine. They may get information from you so they can serve ads that may interest you. They do not take any personal information from you. Typical privacy policies of our major advertisers can be obtained by visiting: 

Please note: Our site may contain links to other sites. Guardster is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Some Guardster services are funded by paid advertisers. All advertising inquiries are handled by email. If you are interested in becoming a paid advertiser please contact us at [support@Guardster.com](mailto:support@Guardster.com). 

If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically. 

**Our Commitment to Data Security**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we may collect online. 

**Our Commitment to Children's Privacy**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never knowingly collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. Visitors younger than 13 years of age may NOT use the Guardster Free webproxy service, the Guardster.com Website, or the Guardster Subscription service. 

**How to Contact Us**  
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please email us at [privacy@Guardster.com](mailto:privacy@Guardster.com).
